I stay up too late
Got nothing in my brain
That's what people say
I go on too many dates
But I can't make them stay
At least that's what people say
That's what people say
But I keep cruising
Can't stop, won't stop moving
It's like I got this music
In my mind, saying it's gonna be alright
Cause the players gonna play, play, play, play, play
And the haters gonna hate, hate, hate, hate, hate
Baby I'm just gonna shake, shake, shake, shake, shake
Shake it off, Shake it off
Heart break is gonna break, break, break, break, break
And I think it's gonna fake, fake, fake, fake, fake
Baby I'm just gonna shake, shake, shake, shake, shake
Shake it off, Shake it off
I never miss a beat
I'm lighting up my feet
And that's what they don't see
That's what they don't see
I'm dancing on my own
I make the moves as I go
And that's what they don't know
That's what they don't know
But I keep cruising
Can't stop, won't stop moving
It's like I got this music
In my mind, saying it's gonna be alright
Cause the players gonna play, play, play, play, play
And the haters gonna hate, hate, hate, hate, hate
Baby I'm just gonna shake, shake, shake, shake, shake
Shake it off, Shake it off
Heart break is gonna break, break, break, break, break
And I think it's gonna fake, fake, fake, fake, fake
Baby I'm just gonna shake, shake, shake, shake, shake
Shake it off, Shake it off
Just think while you been getting down and out about the liars And the dirty dirty cheats of the world
You could have been getting down to this sick beat
My ex man brought his new girlfriend
She's like oh my god
But I'm just gonna shake
And to the fella over there with the hella good hair
Won't you come on over baby we could shake, shake, shake
Cause the players gonna play, play, play, play, play
And the haters gonna hate, hate, hate, hate, hate
Baby I'm just gonna shake, shake, shake, shake, shake
Shake it off, Shake it off
Heart break is gonna break, break, break, break, break
And I think it's gonna fake, fake, fake, fake, fake
Baby I'm just gonna shake, shake, shake, shake, shake
Shake it off, Shake it off
Subtitle By .: Arman333 :.